Guide to the T. W. Anderson Papers SC0911
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
T. W. Anderson papers
1946-2005
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Anderson, T. W. (Theodore Wilbur), 1918-
SC0911
83 Linear Feet (37 boxes)
The papers, which consist of files from Anderson's classes in statistics and economics, contain syllabi, homework, exams, handouts, lecture notes, student evaluations, and other materials.
Information about Access
The collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
T. W. Anderson is Professor Emeritus in the Department of Statistics, Stanford University.
Description of the Collection
The papers, which consist of files from Anderson's classes in statistics and economics, contain syllabi, homework, exams, handouts, lecture notes, student evaluations, and other materials.
Statistics -- Study and teaching.; Statistics -- Study and teaching.; Stanford University. Department of Statistics; Anderson, T. W. (Theodore Wilbur), 1918-; Anderson, T. W. (Theodore Wilbur), 1918-; Stanford University. Department of Statistics; Anderson, T. W. (Theodore Wilbur), 1918-; Anderson, T. W. (Theodore Wilbur), 1918-; Anderson, T. W. (Theodore Wilbur), 1918-
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2008-238
  - Stats 60: Lecture Notes, 1920-1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stats 60: Miscellaneous, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Stats 60: Handouts, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Stats 60: Handouts, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Stats 324B: Miscellaneous, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Stats 324B: Handouts, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Stats 324A: Lectures, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Stats 324A: Final and Analysis, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - M.A. 324B: Lectures, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - M.A. 324B: Winter Quarter Final Exam, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - M.A. 324A: Student Evaluations, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - M.A. 324B: Student Evaluations, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Stats 207; Data, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - M.A. 324A: Exam, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - M.A. 324B: Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - M.A. 324A: Materials, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Stats 324B: Final Exam, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - M.A. 324A: Lectures, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - M.A. 324A: Final, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Stats 324A: Handouts I, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Stats 324A; Handouts II, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - M.A. 324A: Questionnaire-Autumn, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - M.A. 324A: Miscellaneous, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - M.A. 324B: Lectures, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Stats 207: Handouts, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Using Minitab at Lots-Instruction Manual (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Stats 207: Handouts, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Stats 207: Lectures, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Stats 207: Printouts, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Stats 207: Handouts, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Stats 207: Miscellaneous, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Stats 207: Final Exam, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Stats 60: Student Evaluations, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Stats 60: Exercises & Solutions, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Stats 60: Final Exam, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Stats 60: Printouts, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Stats 60: Student Evaluations, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Stats 207: Lectures 1-11, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Stats 207: Lectures 12-20, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Stats 207: Lectures 21-28, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Stats 207: My Exercises, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Stats 207: Exercises, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Stats 60: Lectures, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Stats 60: Lectures, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stats 60: Miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stats 60: My Copies of Handouts, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Stats 60: Handouts, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Stats 60: My Copy of Handouts, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Stats 60: Problems for 2nd Edition, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Stats 60: Final, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Stats 60: Midterm, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Stats 60: Minitab, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Stats 60: Second Edition, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Stats 60: "Next Time", 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Stats 60: Connections to Text, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Stats 60: Problems-Peter Cooke, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Stats 60: First Midterm, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Stats 60: Second Midterm, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Stats 61-161: Exam, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stats 60: Chernoff Materials, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stats 60: Miller Materials-Fall, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Stats 60: Exercises, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Stats 60: Lectures, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Stats 60: Exercises and Solutions, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Stats 60: Miscellaneous Handouts, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Stats 60: Computer Assignments, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Stats 60: Miscellaneous, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Stats 62-162: Miscellaneous, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Stats 62-162: Final Exam, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Stats 62-162: Answers, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Stats 61-161: Handouts and Midterm, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Stats 61-161: Lectures to Midterm, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stats 61-161: Lectures since Midterm (1 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 2-3)
  - Stats 61-161: Midterm Notes, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Stats 61-161: My Copies of Handouts, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Stats 61-161: Miscellaneous, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Stats 60: Handouts, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Stats 60: Midterm, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Stats 60: Final, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Stats 60: Notes for Book, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Stats 60: Evaluations (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Stats 62-262: Handouts (Box 6, Folder 12-13)
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2008-287
  - Econ 273: lecture notes, winter 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Econ 272: lectures, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Econ 272: handouts, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Econ 272: miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Econ 272: handouts, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Econ 272: "my copies of handouts", 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Econ 272:, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Econ 272: evaluations, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Econ 273: notes, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Econ 273: lectures, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Econ 273: handouts, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Econ 273: final exam, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Econ 273: evaluations, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Econ 273: solutions to final exam, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Amemiya, Takeshi - ch. 1, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Scope and Contents note
    Contains only a note from Takeshi.
  - Amemiya: references (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Econ 273: revising notes (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Econ 273: miscellaneous, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Econ 273: lectures 1-10, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Econ 273: lectures 11-17, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Econ 273: "my exercises and handouts", 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Econ 273: exercises, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Econ 273: handouts I, time series, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Econ 273: handouts II, Simultaneous Equation Models, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Econ 273: notes, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Econ 273: final exam, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Econ 273: answers to final exam, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Econ 273: course evaluations, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Econ 273: lecture notes, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Econ 273: lecture notes, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Econ 273: Prof. Lau notes [actually mimeographed lectures], 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Kimio Morimune and Naoto Kunitomo: Text Criterion ["Approximate Distributions of Identifiability Test Statistics for Single Structural Equations with Two Endogenous Variables"], 1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Rothenberg, Thomas J. "Multivariate Asymptotic Expansions for Structural Coefficient Estimators", 1977 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Freedman, D., "On Bootstrapping Two-Stage Least-Squares Estimates in Stationary Linear Models", 1984 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Econometrics, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Econ 273: notes for lectures, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Econ 273: exam, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Econ 273: handouts, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Econ 273: answers, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Econ 273: exercises, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Econ 273: miscellaneous, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Econ 273: final exam, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Econ 273: miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Econ 273: exercises, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Dreze and Richard, discussion paper (Bayesian Analysis of Simultaneous Equation Systems), 1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Econ 272: topics, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Econ 273: student comment on notes, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Econ 273: my copies [syllabi materials], 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Econ 273: course evaluations, winter 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Econ II: final exam, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Econ II: miscellaneous, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Econ II: my copies and handouts, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Econ II: lectures, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Econ II: exercise and solutions, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Econometrics II: notes in revision, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Econ 273: student evaluations, winter 1981 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Econometrics II: final exam, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Econometrics II: questionnaires, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Econometrics II: notes and miscellany, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Econometrics file, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Econometrics II: student suggestions (midterm), 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Econometrics II: course evaluations, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Econometrics II: final exam, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Econometrics II: final exam, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Econometrics II: student course evaluations [winter, no year noted] (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Econometrics II: student course evaluations, winter 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Stats 207: miscellaneous, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - TSA [Time Series Analysis] (Stats 343B): final exam, winter 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - TSA lectures, winter 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Econometrics II: final exam, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Econometrics II: student course evaluations, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Econometrics-273: miscellaneous, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Econometrics-273: student course evaluations (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - TSA (Stats 242A), autumn 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - TSA (Stats 242A) Final exam, autumn 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - TSA (Stats 242B): lectures, winter 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - TSA (Stats 242B): exam, winter 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Stats 219H: lecture notes and final exam, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Stats 219H: final exam and notes, winter 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - TSA (Stats 343A): final exam, autumn 1971 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - TSA lectures fall, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Statistics notes, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Carnegie-Mellon University correspondence, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Stats 343A: student course evaluations, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Stats 207: handouts, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Stats 207: final exam, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Class roll books and some completed student exams removed from this accession's folders [restricted] (Box 6)
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2017-093
  - Subject Files
    - A - Miscellaneous, 1979-1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - A Bibliography of Multivariate Statistical Analysis, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - A Bibliography of Multivariate Statistical Analysis - Reviews, 1973-1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Academic Press, Inc., 1969-1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Academic Press: Elementary Book, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Addison-Wesley Publishing Co., Inc., 1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Addison-Wesley: Correspondence with Publishers, 1958-1967 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Addison-Wesley: Elementary Book, 1967-1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Air Force Office of Scientific Research Proposal, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1981-1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science - Nominating Com., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - American Association of University Professors AAUP, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - American Biographical Institute (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - American Mathematical Society, 1983-1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - American Math Society, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - American Men and Women of Science, 1970-1981 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - American Statistical Association Committee on Elections, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - American Statistical Association Conference Board of the Mathematical Sciences, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - American Statistical Association Joint Statistical Meetings, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - American Statistical Association Correspondence, 1980-1986 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - American University in Cairo, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - An Introduction to the Statistical Analysis of Data - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Anals of Statistics, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Army Research Office Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - ARO, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - ARO Budget, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - ARO Proposal, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - ARO Report, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - ARO Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - ARO, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - ARO, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - ARO Grant Award Sponsored Projects Office, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Army Research Office - Correspondence Dr. Robert Launer, 1982-1988 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Army Research Office Proposal, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Army Research Office Proposal, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Army Research Office - Progress Reports, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Arrow, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - ASA - Census - NBR Conference - Applied Time Series Anal. Of Econ. Data, 1981 Oct 13-15 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Association of University Teachers of Economics Aute, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - B - Miscellaneous, 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Bernoulli Society for Mathematical Statistics and Probability, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Biography International (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Biographical listings (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Biometric Society, 1974-1981 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Biometrics, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Biometrika, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Blaisdell Publishing Company, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Brailovsky (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - C - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Cairo University, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - California Institute of Technology Correspondence, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - California Institute of Technology Office of the Provost, 1978-1981 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Canadian Conference in Applied Statistics, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Census Bureau - Ad hoc committee for effective census bureau management (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Communications in Statistics (Series C) (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Conference Board of the Mathematical Sciences, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - CBMS, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - CBMS Nominations Committee, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences, 1983-1988 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Colproe - Latinamerican Committee to Promote International Relations in Statistics, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Columbia University Press, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Committee of Concerned Scientists, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Conference on Reliability Quality Control (University of Missouri-Columbia), 1984 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Cowles Commission (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - CSIRO, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - D - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Dekker (Marcell, INC.), 1980 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Dictionary of International Biography, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Directory of Distinguished Americans (American Biographical Institute), 1983 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Dover Publications, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - E - Miscellaneous, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Econometric society, 1969-1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Econometric Theory, 1985-1996 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Econometrica, 1976-1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Econometrica refereeing, 1970-1984 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Economics, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Elsevier, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - European Meeting of Statisticians (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - European Meeting of Statisticians - Grenoble, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - European Meeting of Statisticians - Prague, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - F - Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Fullbright - Hays program, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - G - Miscellaneous, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - George Washington University - Continuing Engineering Education Program, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Government-University partnership in science (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - H - Miscellaneous, 1971-1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Hamilton publ. co.: elementary book, 1971 Dec (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Harper Row: Elementary Book, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Holden-day, Inc., 1967-1971 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Holt, Rinehart and Winston, Inc., 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Holt, Rinehart Winston: Elementary Book, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Holt, Rinehart Winston: (TSA), 1967 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Houghton-Mifflin: Author's Alterations, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Houghton-Mifflin: Author's information form, 1972-1977 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Houghton-Mifflin: Cartoons, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Houghton Mifflin: copy-edited/Ch 1 2, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Houghton-Mifflin (on figures), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Houghton-Mifflin: style sheet and sample pages, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Houghton Mifflin - correspondence, 1972-1978 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Houghton Mifflin (William H. Berman), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Houghton-Mifflin - David G. Bergguist, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Houghton-Mifflin - Nancy Hirose Brooks, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Houghton-Mifflin - W. M. Buddenhagen, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Houghton-Mifflin: Buddenhagen-Cassette, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Houghton-Mifflin - Sarah A. Ciriello, 1974 July (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Houghton-Mifflin - Mark S. Cowell (correspondence), 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Houghton- Mifflin - Robert C. Dickinson, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Houghton Mifflin (Robert Domosh), 1977 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Houghton Mifflin (WM. J. Fitzgerald), 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Houghton Mifflin (Bill Karjane), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Houghton-Mifflin: Karjane Sclove - correspondence, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Houghton-Mifflin Co. -Paul Kelly, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Houghton Mifflin (A. W. Kingston), 1979-1985 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Houghton-Mifflin: W. D. MacDonald correspondence, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Houghton-Mifflin - (Veronica McLoud), 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Houghton Mifflin (Harold T. Miller), 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Houghton-Mifflin (Ms. Marcia Mirsky), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Houghton Mifflin (Anne A. Reid), 1977 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Houghton-Mifflin - Pamela Rockwell- correspondence, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Houghton-Mifflin - Irving Rockwood, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Houghton-Mifflin - Jeffrey Sund- correspondence, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Houghton-Mifflin: Frank P. Satlow, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Houghton-Mifflin - PA (Thompson), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Houghton Mifflin (Robert West), 1977 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Houghton Mifflin (Susan Winkler), 1977 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Institute of Mathematical Statistics, 1970-1979 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Institute of Mathematical Statistics, 1958-1969 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Indian Statistical Institute, 1976-1986 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Institute of Mathematical Statistics Committee on Graduate Fellowships, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - IMSSS, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - IBM-SRI (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - I - Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Institute of Mathematical Statistics - Committee on Operations, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Institute of Mathematical Statistics- Committee on Operations, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Institute of Mathematical Statistics Council, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Institute of Mathematical Statistics Executive Committee, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Institute of Mathematical Statistics Hotelling Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Institute of Mathematical Statistics Publications Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Institute of Statistical Mathematics, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - The 12th International Biometric Conference (IBC), 1984 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - IBM, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - International conference on the unity of the sciences (ICUS), 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - International Statistical Information (newsletter), 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - International Statistical Institute 37th Season - London, 1969 Sep (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - International Who's Who (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - International Who's Who of Intellectuals (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - ISI Manila Meeting - "Some Relations between Markov Chains and Vector Autoregressive Processes", 1979 Dec 4-14 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - S-906 Invitations Declined, 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - International Statistical Institute Correspondence/Reports, 1969-1980 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - International Statistical Institute List of members, 1978-1985 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - J - Miscellaneous, 1968-1988 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Joint Statistical meeting, 1985 Aug 5-8 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - JASA Journal of the American Statistical Association, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Journal of Econometrics, 1979-1986 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Journal of Multivariate Analysis, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Journal of Multivariate Analysis (advisory board) (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Journal of Time Series Analysis (also see Tieto, Ltd.), 1983 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - K - Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Karlin Volume contributors: correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Karlin Volume Academic Press: Eris Kramer, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Karlin Volume Academic Press: Susan J. McCulley, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Karlin volume Academic Press: Klaus Peters, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Karlin Volume Co-Editor: Krishna Athreya, 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Karlin Volume Co-Editor: Donald Iglehart, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Karlin Volume Co-Editors: Memorandums, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Karlin Volume Contributors: Memorandums (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Karlin Volume Contributors: Responses, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Karlin Volume Format: Cover/Title Pages, 1989 June (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Karlin Volume Format: Specifications (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Karlin Volume Format: Trial TEX, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Karlin Volume Samuel Karlin: Biography (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Karlin Volume Samuel: Publications (Box 3, Folder 36)